Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files F-J, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files
  - Subject Files F
    - Francois, Joseph (Box A-43, Folder 141)
      1 print taped to cardboard.
    - Francois, Tchands L. Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-43, Folder 142)
    - Francois, Mr. & Mrs. Theodore (Box A-43, Folder 143)
    - Frank, Bill (Box A-43, Folder 144)
    - Frank, Harry B. (Box A-43, Folder 145)
      Photographer if identified: Cecil Layne, Burley Photo Syndicate,
    - Frank, James Dr. (Box A-43, Folder 146)
    - Frank, Marjorie (Box A-43, Folder 147)
    - Wills, Frank (Box A-43, Folder 148)
    - Frankel, Jean (Box A-43, Folder 149)
    - Franklin, Adele (Box A-43, Folder 150)
    - Franklin, Anderson J. (Box A-43, Folder 151)
      Print has a staple through the border.
    - Franklin, Anna (Mrs.) (Box A-43, Folder 152)
    - Franklin, Anne M. (Box A-43, Folder 153)
      Photographer if identified: Morris Hattem
    - Franklin, Aretha (Box A-43, Folder 154)
    - Franklin, Aretha (Box A-43, Folder 155)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, E. A. Wiggins, Monroe S. Frederick, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, James J. Kriegsmann,
    - Franklin, Aretha (Box A-43, Folder 156)
      Also 9 velox prints. 2 prints have staples through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Rita E. Henderson, Ronnie Brathwaite, Jeffrey Mayer, Bryan D. Hall, James Gilbert,
    - Franklin, Aretha (Box A-43, Folder 157)
      Photographer if identified: Allen Morgan
    - Franklin, Ben (Box A-43, Folder 158)
      Photographer if identified: Vienn & Associates
    - Franklin, Benjamin Finley (Box A-43, Folder 159)
    - Franklin, Buddy (Box A-43, Folder 160)
      Print is a Polaroid.
    - Franklin, Carl (Box A-43, Folder 161)
    - Franklin, Carl M. (Box A-43, Folder 162)
    - Franklin, Carolyn (Box A-43, Folder 163)
    - Franklin, Dolores M. Dr. (Box A-43, Folder 164)
      Photographer if identified: Pach Bros.
    - Don Franklin (Box A-43, Folder 165)
      One print has staple through edge. photocopied newspaper clippings.
    - Franklin, Douglas (Box A-43, Folder 166)
    - Franklin, Douglas A. (Box A-43, Folder 167)
    - Franklin, Dudley (Box A-43, Folder 168)
      Print has staples through edge.
    - Franklin, Ed (Box A-43, Folder 169)
    - Franklin, Ellis (Box A-43, Folder 170)
      Photographer if identified: CARE photo
    - Franklin, Erma (Box A-43, Folder 171)
      Typescript caption stapled to recto of 1 print.
      Photographer if identified: James J. Kriegsmann, Bruno of Hollywood,
    - Franklin, Georgia (Box A-43, Folder 172)
    - Franklin, Joan (Box A-43, Folder 173)
      Photographer if identified: Studio of the New York Times
    - Franklin, Joe (Box A-43, Folder 174)
    - Franklin, John (Box A-43, Folder 175)
      Photographer if identified: N.Y.C. Housing Authority
    - Franklin, John Hope (Box A-43, Folder 176)
      Photographer if identified: Maurice Lehv, Yves/Paris, David J. M. Robinson, Jules Schick, The University of Chicago Office of Public Information
    - Franklin, Karin (Box A-43, Folder 177)
      Photographer if identified: George West
    - Franklin, Levi (Rev.) (Box A-43, Folder 178)
      Photographer if identified: Rufus Merritt
    - Franklin, Melvin (also here is Naomi) (Box A-43, Folder 179)
    - Franklin, Naomi (Box A-43, Folder 180)
    - Franklin, Peter (Box A-43, Folder 181)
    - Franklin, Regina A. (Box A-43, Folder 182)
    - Franklin, Robert B. (Judge) (Box A-43, Folder 183)
    - Franklin, Robin Y. (Box A-43, Folder 184)
    - Franklin, Roosevelt Rev. (Box A-43, Folder 185)
      Ms. caption stapled to verso of print.
    - Franklin, Rudy (Box A-43, Folder 186)
      Print stapled to envelope.
    - Franklin, Sabrina (Box A-43, Folder 187)
    - Franklin, Shirley (Box A-43, Folder 188)
    - Franklin, Wendel (Box A-43, Folder 189)
      Photographer if identified: Floyd McCarthy
    - Franklin, Willa (Box A-43, Folder 190)
    - Franks, Richard Lt. & Mrs. (Box A-43, Folder 191)
      Photographer if identified: Alex Hamilton
    - Franks, Samuel (Box A-43, Folder 192)
      Photographer if identified: Benjamin Franklin
    - Franz, F. W. (Box A-43, Folder 193)
    - Fraser, Abe (Box A-43, Folder 194)
    - Fraser, C. B. (Rev.) (Box A-43, Folder 195)
    - Fraser, Debra (Box A-43, Folder 196)
      Photographer if identified: Bill Moore
    - Fraser, Erroll (Box A-43, Folder 197)
    - Fraser, Gerald (Box A-43, Folder 198)
    - Fraser, George C. (Box A-43, Folder 199)
    - Fraser, Grenaldo (Box A-43, Folder 200)
    - Fraser, Thomas Bishop (Box A-43, Folder 201)
    - Fraser, Trevor (Box A-43, Folder 202)
    - Fraser, Walter Lt. (Box A-43, Folder 203)
      Photographer if identified: Oscar Mallory
    - Frasier, Agnes (Box A-43, Folder 204)
    - Cliff Frasier (Box A-43, Folder 205)
      Photographer if identified: Ali Rahman
    - George Fraser (Box A-43, Folder 206)
    - Frasier, Isaac (Box A-43, Folder 207)
    - Frasier, Michael (Box A-43, Folder 208)
    - Fratianne, Linda (Box A-43, Folder 209)
    - Frauch, Thomas (Box A-43, Folder 210)
    - Frazier, Alexander (Box A-43, Folder 211)
    - Frazier, Adrienne (Box A-43, Folder 212)
    - Frazier, Audrey (Box A-43, Folder 213)
    - Frazier, Boo (Box A-43, Folder 214)
      1 print has typescript caption stapled to recto.
    - Frazier, Bruce (Box A-43, Folder 215)
    - Frazier, Carole (Box A-43, Folder 216)
      Photographer if identified: James Barnett
    - Frazier, Charles (Box A-43, Folder 217)
    - Frazier, Charlie (Box A-43, Folder 218)
    - Frazier, Clifford (Box A-43, Folder 219)
    - Frazier, Clyde (Box A-43, Folder 220)
    - Frazier, Cliff (Box A-43, Folder 221)
      Also several newspaper clippings. 1 print is of Woodie King, Jr.
    - Frazier, Constance L. (Box A-43, Folder 222)
      Photographer if identified: Ted Neuhoff
    - Frazier, Eric (Box A-43, Folder 223)
    - Frazier, Ernest (Box A-43, Folder 224)
    - Frazier, Frances B. (Box A-43, Folder 225)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise
    - Frazier, Frank (Box A-43, Folder 226)
      Photographer if identified: Tri-County Photo Service
    - Frazier, Franklin (Box A-43, Folder 227)
    - Frazier, Gerald T. (Box A-43, Folder 228)
    - Frazier, G. L. (Box A-43, Folder 229)
    - Frazier, Grenoldo (Box A-43, Folder 230)
    - Frazier, Hal (Box A-43, Folder 231)
    - Frazier, Hank (Box A-43, Folder 232)
      Also one velox print. Print has staples.
    - Frazier, Horace (Box A-43, Folder 233)
    - Francis, Innis (Box A-43, Folder 234)
    - Frazier, Ivy (Box A-43, Folder 235)
    - Frazier, J. Basil (Box A-43, Folder 236)
      Photographer if identified: Morgan State College
    - Frazier, James (Box A-43, Folder 237)
      Photographer if identified: Dept. of Transportation, Hamilton Associates, Harris Photo
    - Frazier, James Jr. (Box A-43, Folder 238)
    - Frazier, Joe (Box A-43, Folder 239)
      Also 4 velox prints. 1 print has newspaper clipping taped to verso.
      Photographer if identified: Sy Presten, Dan Miller, James Gilbert, United Press International, Wide World Photos, Harris Photo, Bob Head
    - Frazier, Joe (Box A-43, Folder 240)
      Photographer if identified: Bob Head,
    - Frazier, John (Box A-43, Folder 241)
    - Frazier, Kermit (Box A-43, Folder 242)
    - Frazier, L. D. (Box A-43, Folder 243)
    - Frazier, Lee René (Box A-43, Folder 244)
    - Frazier, Leo (Box A-43, Folder 245)
    - Frazier, Leon Dr. (Box A-43, Folder 246)
    - Frazier, Marlene (Box A-43, Folder 247)
      Photographer if identified: N. J. Chisholm
    - Frazier, Marvis (Box A-43, Folder 248)
    - Frazier, Mary (Box A-43, Folder 249)
    - Frazier, Melvin (Box A-43, Folder 250)
      Photographer if identified: New York Fire Department
    - Frazier, Nathaniel (Box A-43, Folder 251)
    - Frazier, Sam (Box A-43, Folder 252)
      Print has staple, and is a composite of two prints.
    - Frazier, Sharon (Box A-43, Folder 253)
      Photographer if identified: USAF
    - Frazier, Raymond (Box A-43, Folder 254)
    - Frazier, Sheila (Box A-43, Folder 255)
    - Frazier, T. (Box A-43, Folder 256)
    - Frazier, Walt (Basketball Star) (Box A-43, Folder 257)
      Photographer if identified: United Press International, Billy PierceJr., Wide World Photos,
    - Frazier, Wm. Dr. (Box A-43, Folder 258)
    - Frazier, Thomas (Box A-43, Folder 259)
      Also one velox and 2 halftone prints.
      Photographer if identified: Nate Silverstein,
    - Frazier, Vicki (Box A-43, Folder 260)
    - Frazier, Wallace (Box A-43, Folder 261)
      1 print is of Walt Frazier.
    - Freddy's Fire (Box A-43, Folder 262)
    - Frederick, Brenda T. (Box A-43, Folder 263)
    - Frederick, Carlton (Box A-43, Folder 264)
      Photographer if identified: Portfolio International
    - Frederick, Hal (Box A-43, Folder 265)
    - Frederick, Lucille (Box A-43, Folder 266)
    - Frederick, M. S. (Box A-43, Folder 267)
    - Frederick, Norman (Box A-43, Folder 268)
    - Frederick, Ted (Box A-43, Folder 269)
    - Frederick, Warren (Box A-43, Folder 270)
      Photographer if identified: Portrait by Denie
    - Fredericks, Arthur (Box A-43, Folder 271)
    - Fredericks, Bea (Box A-43, Folder 272)
    - Fredericks, Benjamin (Box A-43, Folder 273)
    - Fredericks, Connie (Box A-43, Folder 274)
      Photographer if identified: Bryan Hall
    - Fredericks, Cora (Box A-43, Folder 275)
    - Fredericks, John (Box A-43, Folder 276)
    - Fredericks, Monroe S. (Box A-43, Folder 277)
    - Fredrickson, Donald S. Dr. (Box A-43, Folder 278)
    - Free Expression (Box A-43, Folder 279)
    - Ken Free (Box A-43, Folder 280)
    - Freed, Eugene V. (Box A-43, Folder 281)
      Photographer if identified: Fabian Bachrach
    - Freedman, Florence B. (Box A-43, Folder 282)
    - Freedman, Jacob (Box A-43, Folder 283)
      Photographer if identified: Photomethods Inc.
    - Freedom Elevator Corp. (Box A-43, Folder 284)
    - Freedom Nat'l Bank (Box A-43, Folder 285)
      Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Pictorial Enterprise
      Number of Prints: 14
    - Freedom Nat'l Bank (Box A-43, Folder 286)
      2 prints have a newspaper clipping taped to verso. 2 prints are stuck together with paste.
      Photographer if identified: Bro. David McAdams, Harris Photo, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Alvin J. Burley, Al Ben-Ness, Cecil Layne, James Gilbert, Wagner International Photos, Ed Bagwell, Ace Creative Photo, Rowe, Robert L. Haggins
    - Freedom Nat'l Bank (Box A-43, Folder 287)
      Also Vol. 1 of Freedom Speaks. One print has staple through edge. 1 print has newspaper clipping taped to verso. 4 prints stapled together.
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Cecil Layne, James Gilbert, Negro Press Photo Service, George West
      Number of Prints: 29
    - Phenomenal Photographs of Freedom (Box A-43, Folder 288)
    - Freedom, Riders (Box A-44, Folder 1)
    - Freedom, Singers (Box A-44, Folder 2)
    - Freeland, John (Mr & Mrs) (Box A-44, Folder 3)
    - Freeman, Al (Box A-44, Folder 4)
      9 prints have typescript leaves affixed to the verso.
      Photographer if identified: Pope Studio
    - Freeman, Andrea L. (Box A-44, Folder 5)
    - Freeman, Annette (Box A-44, Folder 6)
    - Freeman, Annie (Box A-44, Folder 7)
    - Freeman, Barbara (Box A-44, Folder 8)
      Photographer if identified: David Greene
    - Freeman, Arnold (Box A-44, Folder 9)
    - Freeman, Austin E. (Box A-44, Folder 10)
      Photographer if identified: Gill Photography
    - Freeman, Bert (Box A-44, Folder 11)
    - Freeman, Blossom Bernice (Box A-44, Folder 12)
      One envelope attached with a paperclip to verso of print.
    - Freeman, Bobby (Box A-44, Folder 13)
    - Freeman, Bud (Box A-44, Folder 14)
      Photographer if identified: Metro Opera Assn Inc
    - Freeman, Carl (Box A-44, Folder 15)
    - Freeman, Cheryl (Box A-44, Folder 16)
    - Freeman, Chris (Box A-44, Folder 17)
    - Freeman, Claretta (Box A-44, Folder 18)
    - Freeman, Clyde (Dr) (Box A-44, Folder 19)
    - Freeman, Corine A. (Box A-44, Folder 20)
    - Freeman, Darryl (Box A-44, Folder 21)
      Photographer if identified: Gus Wartell
    - Freeman, Diane (Box A-44, Folder 22)
      Photographer if identified: Bro David McAdams
    - Freman, Doris (Box A-44, Folder 23)
    - Freeman, Douglas (Box A-44, Folder 24)
    - Freeman, Enrigue (Box A-44, Folder 25)
    - Freeman, Evelyn (Box A-44, Folder 26)
      One print has a staple through the border.
      Photographer if identified: Joe Zinn, Cecil Layne, Harris Photo
    - Freeman, Frannie (Mrs) (Box A-44, Folder 27)
    - Freeman, Frankie (Box A-44, Folder 28)
      One computer-printed typescript leaf tapped to verso of print
      Photographer if identified: Al Lane
    - Freeman, Frankie (Box A-44, Folder 29)
    - Freeman, George (Box A-44, Folder 30)
    - Freeman, George (Mrs.) (Box A-44, Folder 31)
    - Freeman, Gloria (Box A-44, Folder 32)
      Photographer if identified: Gloud Photos
    - Freeman, Harold (Dr.) (Box A-44, Folder 33)
    - Freeman, Helen (Box A-44, Folder 34)
      Photographer if identified: Curt Clemons, M Associates,
    - Freeman, J.T (Box A-44, Folder 35)
    - Freeman, Jasper J. (Rev) (Box A-44, Folder 36)
      Photographer if identified: Modern Arts Studio
    - Freeman, James (Box A-44, Folder 37)
    - Freeman, Jeffery (Box A-44, Folder 38)
      Partial print stuck to folder.
    - Freeman, Jewel (Box A-44, Folder 39)
    - Freeman, Julius (Mr & Mrs.) (Box A-44, Folder 40)
    - Freeman, Karene (Box A-44, Folder 41)
    - Freeman, Kenn (Box A-44, Folder 42)
    - Freeman, Kenny (Box A-44, Folder 43)
    - Freeman, Madelyn (Mrs.) (Box A-44, Folder 44)
    - Freeman, Monica (Box A-44, Folder 45)
      Photographer if identified: Maya Sharpe
    - Freeman, Morgan (Box A-44, Folder 46)
    - Freeman, Nathaniel (Box A-44, Folder 47)
    - Freeman, Orville L. (Box A-44, Folder 48)
    - Freeman, Paul (Box A-44, Folder 49)
      One print has a ms. leaf with a sketch stapled to recto. Also one velox print.
      Photographer if identified: Ester Brown
    - Freeman, Phyllis B. (Box A-44, Folder 50)
    - Freeman, Reginald A. (Box A-44, Folder 51)
    - Freeman, Robert T. (Box A-44, Folder 52)
      Photographer if identified: J. Lovett
    - Freeman, Roy (Box A-44, Folder 53)
    - Freeman, Sarah (Mrs.) (Box A-44, Folder 54)
    - Freeman, Steve (Box A-44, Folder 55)
    - Freeman, Ted (Box A-44, Folder 56)
    - Freeman, Theodore (Box A-44, Folder 57)
    - Freeman, Thoma (Box A-44, Folder 58)
    - Freeman, Thoman (Box A-44, Folder 59)
    - Freeman, Valda (Box A-44, Folder 60)
    - Freeman, Varney (Box A-44, Folder 61)
    - Freeman, Von (Box A-44, Folder 62)
    - Freeman, Adrian W. (Box A-44, Folder 63)
    - Freeman, W.A (Dr.) (Box A-44, Folder 64)
    - Freeman, William (Box A-44, Folder 65)
    - Freeman, Wiliams R. (Rev.) (Box A-44, Folder 66)
    - Freeman, Hospital (Box A-44, Folder 67)
    - Freeman, Yvette (Box A-44, Folder 68)
      Photographer if identified: Martha Swope
    - Freiburg, Lowell (Box A-44, Folder 69)
    - Friedan, Betty (Box A-44, Folder 70)
    - Freidman, Alvin (Box A-44, Folder 71)
    - Freitas, Ericde (Box A-44, Folder 72)
      Photographer if identified: Bob Olen Studio
    - Freiwirth, Martin (Box A-44, Folder 73)
    - Fremon, Claretta (Box A-44, Folder 74)
    - French, Arthur (Box A-44, Folder 75)
      Photographer if identified: Bert Andrews
    - French, Arthur W. 3 (Box A-44, Folder 76)
    - French, Chester (Box A-44, Folder 77)
    - French, David (Dr.) (Box A-44, Folder 78)
    - French, Desiree (Box A-44, Folder 79)
    - French, John (Box A-44, Folder 80)
    - French, Muriel (Box A-44, Folder 81)
    - French, Patricia (Box A-44, Folder 82)
    - French, Pearline (Box A-44, Folder 83)
      Also 2 newspaper clippings.
    - French, Selvyn H. (Box A-44, Folder 84)
    - Frenchy (Box A-44, Folder 85)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Al Burley, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise
    - Frender, Marilyn (Box A-44, Folder 86)
    - Freschil, Marion Szekely (Mrs.) (Box A-44, Folder 87)
      Photographer if identified: Whitestone
    - Fresh, Air Fund (Box A-44, Folder 88)
      One print has an ms. text written on the verso.
    - Fresh, Doug E. (Box A-44, Folder 89)
    - Fresh, Prince (Box A-44, Folder 90)
      2 prints are attached together with a staple.
    - Frett, James (Box A-44, Folder 91)
    - Frett, Narcissus D. (Box A-44, Folder 92)
    - Frettwell, Gloria Jean (Box A-44, Folder 93)
    - Frey, Martha (Box A-44, Folder 94)
    - Friday, 13th pt 2 (Box A-44, Folder 95)
    - Friday, Foster (Box A-44, Folder 96)
    - Friday, H. J. Wilfred (Box A-44, Folder 97)
    - Fried, Abraham (Box A-44, Folder 98)
    - Fried, Ken (Box A-44, Folder 99)
    - Friedan, Betty (Box A-44, Folder 100)
    - Friedman, Gretchen (Box A-44, Folder 101)
    - Friedman, Howard (Box A-44, Folder 102)
    - Friedman, James (Ph.) (Box A-44, Folder 103)
    - Friedman, Nat (Box A-44, Folder 104)
    - Friends of Distraction (Box A-44, Folder 105)
    - Friendship Baptist Chruch (Box A-44, Folder 106)
      3 prints have staples through the border.
      Photographer if identified: Ace Creative Photo
    - Friendship House (Box A-44, Folder 107)
    - Frierson, Andrew (Box A-44, Folder 108)
      Also 2 halftone prints.
    - Frierson, Grover C. (Box A-44, Folder 110)
    - Frisby, Herbert M. (Box A-44, Folder 111)
    - Frith, Raymond (Box A-44, Folder 112)
    - Fritz, Pelham (Box A-44, Folder 113)
    - Froelch, Martha (Box A-44, Folder 114)
    - Frog (Box A-44, Folder 115)
    - Frontiersmen (Box A-44, Folder 116)
      One print has 3 computer-printed typescript leaves taped to the verso. 2 prints have typescript leaves attached with paperclips. One print has an ms. text written on the verso.
      Photographer if identified: S.K Bryson Photography, Cecil Layne, Bro David McAdams, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise
    - Frontiersmen (Box A-44, Folder 117)
    - Front Line (Box A-44, Folder 118)
      Four computer typescript leaves stapled to verso of print.
    - Frost, Alvin (Box A-44, Folder 119)
    - Frost, Charles S. (Box A-44, Folder 120)
    - Frost, David (Box A-44, Folder 121)
    - Frost, Huge A (Box A-44, Folder 122)
      Photographer if identified: United International Photo
    - Frost, James (Box A-44, Folder 123)
    - Frost, John B. (Box A-44, Folder 124)
    - Frost, Olivia (Mrs.) (Box A-44, Folder 125)
    - Foster Band, Wm.P (Box A-44, Folder 126)
    - Frye, Edna (Box A-44, Folder 127)
    - Frye, George (Box A-44, Folder 128)
      Photographer if identified: George Frye
    - Frye, Henry E. (Box A-44, Folder 129)
    - Frye, Marion (Box A-44, Folder 130)
      One halftone print.
    - Frye, Thomas M. (Box A-44, Folder 131)
      Photographer if identified: Taylor Made Photo
    - Frye, Ronald (Box A-44, Folder 132)
    - Fryer, Emily (Box A-44, Folder 133)
    - Fryer, James (Box A-44, Folder 134)
      Photographer if identified: Edmond J. Murray
    - Fuchberg, Jacob (Rev.) (Box A-44, Folder 135)
    - Fuell, Eugnia (Mrs.) (Box A-44, Folder 136)
    - Fuentes, Jose (Box A-44, Folder 137)
      Also one small leaf of ms. notes and 3 computer-printed typescript leaves
    - Fuentes, Louis A. (Box A-44, Folder 138)
    - Fuentes, Luis A. (Box A-44, Folder 139)
    - Fugees (Box A-44, Folder 140)
    - Frugges, Wyclef (Box A-44, Folder 141)
    - Fugua, Sandra (Box A-44, Folder 142)
    - Fujihira, Loge (Box A-44, Folder 143)
      Photographer if identified: United Methodist missions
    - Fulani, Lenora (Box A-44, Folder 144)
      One print has 2 computer-printed leaves attached with a paperclip. Also two typescript leaves and 2 halftone prints.
      Photographer if identified: Peterkin Photo, Bill Moore
    - Fulani, Lenora (Dr.) (Box A-44, Folder 145)
    - Fulani, Lenora (Box A-44, Folder 146)
    - Fulana, Kenneth (Box A-44, Folder 147)
    - Fulbright, Stewart (Dr.) (Box A-44, Folder 148)
    - Fulcher, Anna C. (Mrs.) (Box A-44, Folder 149)
    - Fulford, James F (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-44, Folder 150)
      Ms. text written on verso of print.
    - Fulgate, Mary (Box A-44, Folder 151)
    - Fulgham, Helen Diane (Box A-44, Folder 152)
    - Fuller, Alvin, The dancers (Box A-44, Folder 153)
    - Fuller, Albert A. (Box A-44, Folder 154)
    - Fuller, Anthony (Dr.) (Box A-44, Folder 155)
    - Fuller, Bertha B. (Box A-44, Folder 156)
    - Fuller, Charle (Box A-44, Folder 157)
      Photographer if identified: Tyrone Rasheed
    - Fuller, Charles (Box A-44, Folder 158)
    - Fuller, Eileen (Box A-44, Folder 159)
    - Fuller, Ellen (Box A-44, Folder 160)
    - Fuller, Frank (Rev.) (Box A-44, Folder 161)
    - Fuller, Howard (Box A-44, Folder 162)
    - Fuller, Jesse (lone cat) (Box A-44, Folder 163)
    - Fuller, Josiah R. (Box A-44, Folder 164)
    - Fuller, Judy P. (Mrs.) (Box A-44, Folder 165)
    - Fuller, Leonard 2 (Box A-44, Folder 166)
    - Fuller, Ronald (Box A-44, Folder 167)
    - Fuller, Telemachus (Box A-44, Folder 168)
      Photographer if identified: Fay Foto Services
    - Fuller, Vickie (Box A-44, Folder 169)
    - Full force (Box A-44, Folder 170)
    - Fulllove, Helen (Mrs.) (Box A-44, Folder 171)
    - Fullwood, Harlow (Box A-44, Folder 172)
      Photographer if identified: Richard H. Barrett
    - Fulmore, Kenneth (Box A-44, Folder 173)
    - Fulson, Jean (Box A-44, Folder 174)
    - Fulton, Lowell (Box A-44, Folder 175)
      One paper stereotype matrix.
    - Fulton, George (Box A-44, Folder 176)
    - Fultry, Louise (Box A-44, Folder 177)
    - Fuetz, Lionel (Box A-44, Folder 178)
      Photographer if identified: James, Gilbert
    - Fuetz, James H. (Box A-44, Folder 179)
    - Fultz, Quad Ruplets (Box A-44, Folder 180)
      Four prints are attached together with a staple. One print has a typescript leaf attached with a paperclip. Also one typescript leaf and one halftone print.
      Photographer if identified: Capitol Photo serivces,
    - Fullwood, Preston (Box A-44, Folder 181)
    - Funches, Ethel (Box A-44, Folder 182)
    - Funderburk, Thomas (Box A-44, Folder 183)
    - Funerburk, William W. (Dr.) (Box A-44, Folder 184)
    - Fundarburg, Owen. I (Box A-44, Folder 185)
    - Funerals (Box A-44, Folder 186)
    - Funeral, Directors (Box A-44, Folder 187)
      Photographer if identified: L.Moyse, Pope Studio, Shotski Jones Studio, King Photography
    - Funicello, Annette (Box A-44, Folder 188)
    - Funkadelics (Box A-44, Folder 189)
      One velox print and one halftone print.
    - Funky Four + 1 more (Box A-44, Folder 190)
    - Fung, Gorgon (Box A-44, Folder 191)
    - Funn, Arthur (Box A-44, Folder 192)
    - Funnye, Clarence (Box A-44, Folder 193)
      Photographer if identified: Studio of New York Times
    - Funny house of la Negro (Box A-44, Folder 194)
    - Funn, Arthur (Box A-44, Folder 195)
    - Fugua, Harvey (Box A-44, Folder 196)
    - Fungason, Sylverster (Box A-44, Folder 197)
    - Furham, Ben (Box A-44, Folder 198)
    - Fulow, Bosie (Mr + Mrs.) (Box A-44, Folder 199)
    - Furman, Frankie (Box A-44, Folder 200)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, James Gilbert
    - Furman, Roger (Box A-44, Folder 201)
      Also one typescript leaf and one halftone print.
    - Furniture (Box A-44, Folder 202)
      Also 3 halftone prints and one packet of typescript leaves. One print is mounted.
    - Furess, Betty (Box A-44, Folder 203)
      Photographer if identified: Whitestone, Erman's Studio
    - Fuis, Mildred (Box A-44, Folder 204)
    - Fusee, Fred G. (Box A-44, Folder 205)
    - Futch, Wally (singers) (Box A-44, Folder 206)
    - Futrell, Diane (Box A-44, Folder 207)
    - Futrell, James (Box A-44, Folder 208)
    - Negros, In Alaska (Box A-44, Folder 209)